For this quiz I want you to practice writing your first HTML
في هذا الاختبار، أريدك أن تتدرب على كتابة أول عناصر HTML
elements kind of like this one.
الذي يشبه هذا.
And just a reminder, this is the structure of an element.
تذكر أن، هذه بنية العنصر.
There's the opening tag, the content which is going to be text here and
ها هي العلامة الافتتاحية، ثم المحتوى الذي هو النص هنا
then the closing tag and notice the closing tag has the slash in it.
وعلامة الإغلاق ولاحظ أن علامة الإغلاق تحتوي على الشرطة المائلة.
Okay, here's your challenge.
حسنًا، ها هو التحدي لك.
For this quiz I want you to create three elements.
في هذا الاختبار، أريدك أن تقوم بإنشاء ثلاثة عناصر.
And i want one of them to be a paragraph and then two of them to be spans.
وأريد واحد منهم ليكون paragraph واثنين لتكون spans.
The names paragraph and
الأسماء paragraph
span tell you a little bit how these two elements will look on the page.
وspan تخبرك قليلاً كيف سيبدو هاذين العنصرين على الصفحة.
A paragraph is a literal paragraph like from writing.
paragraph هو فقرة حرفية مثل الكتابة.
It's a big block of text that is separate from other pieces of text.
هو كتلة كبيرة من النصوص منفصلة عن أجزاء أخرى من النص.
A span is like a line of text and
span هو مثل سطر من النص
it isn't really separate from other pieces of text.
وليس منفصلاً عن الأجزاء الأخرى من النص.
Try playing around with both of these tags to see how they look.
حاول العبث بهاتين العلامتين لترى كيف ستبدوان.
And when you're working on your elements,
وبينما تعمل على العناصر التي تكتبها،
you can put whatever content you like inside of them.
يمكنك وضع المحتوى الذي تريده بداخلهما.
It doesn't matter so
لا يهم طالما
long as something is there, your answer will be counted as correct.
تضع شيء ما هنا، ستُعتبر إجابتك صحيحة.
And you may be wondering if you can put all the elements on the same line of
وربما تتساءل هل بإمكانك وضع كل العناصر على نفس السطر
text, or if they need to be different lines.
أو يجب أن يكونوا في سطور مختلفة.
My advice is to try both and then see what happens.
نصيحتي هي أن تجرب الأمرين وترى ما سيحدث.
All right good luck, I know you can do this.
حسنًا، حظًا موفقًا أعلم أنك قادرًا على فعلها.
All you need to do is type out tags just like this one but with paragraphs and
كل ما تحتاج لفعله هو أن تكتب العلامات مثل هذه لكن مع paragraphs
spans, and you'll be okay.
وspans، وستكون بخير.
You've got this.
لقد فهمتَ ذلك.